Step 1: click (715, 181) [OK]\NI need to search for "人工知能" (artificial intelligence in Japanese). I can see a Wikipedia page in Japanese with a search
Step 2: click (700, 180) [OK]\NI can see the Wikipedia homepage in Japanese. In the task history, I see that Step 1 was a click at coordinates (715, 18
Step 3: click (715, 180) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Wikipedia Japanese homepage. The task history shows I've clicked twice already,
Step 4: find_and_click (855, 195) [OK]\NI can see the Wikipedia Japanese homepage. Looking at the task history, I've been clicking at coordinates around (715, 1
Step 5: type  [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Wikipedia Japanese homepage. The search box is visible at the top of the page w
Step 6: click (937, 180) [OK]\NI can see the Wikipedia Japanese homepage with the search box visible at the top. The search box contains the text '人工知能
Step 7: click (949, 348) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The search box in the center of the page conta
Step 8: click (945, 180) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The search box at the top shows '人工知能' (artifi
Step 9: click (720, 180) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The task history shows I've been clicking at v
Step 10: click (949, 348) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The task history shows I've been clicking vari
Step 11: click (585, 346) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The search box at the top shows 'Wikipedia内を検索
Step 12: find_and_click (840, 192) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The search box at the top of the page is empty
Step 13: type  [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The search box at the top of the page is visib
Step 14: click (945, 180) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The search box at the top contains '人工知能' (art
Step 15: click (945, 180) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The search box at the top of the page contains
Step 16: click (949, 348) [OK]\NI can see the Wikipedia search page in Japanese. Looking at the screen, I notice there's a search input field with text
Step 17: click (943, 180) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The search input field at the top of t
Step 18: find_and_click (840, 195) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The search input field at the top of the page
Step 19: click (943, 180) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. The search input box at the top of the page cu
Step 20: click (949, 348) [OK]\NI can see a Wikipedia search page in Japanese. Looking at the screen, I notice there's a search input box at the top wit